[SPEAKER_02]: You were born here in Napa or Napa?
[SPEAKER_01]: Napa.
[SPEAKER_02]: In January 16th, 1894?
[SPEAKER_02]: 95.
[SPEAKER_02]: Record book says 94, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, right.
[SPEAKER_02]: 83, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: 83, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: 83 left, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did your family always live here?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, they all lived here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And did your father play ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a farmer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where did his father come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: Someplace else?
[SPEAKER_01]: Italy.
[SPEAKER_01]: He came from Italy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he was?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: How'd he happen to settle out here, I wonder?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this is a wine country, you know, and there's a lot of Italians settled here from Italy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you'll find, if you look through the phone book, you'll see a lot of Italian names.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fourth and fifth generation.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's the time they used to have gold.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least I can think of five hotels that are run by Italian, poor Italian people.
[SPEAKER_01]: They work in the vineyards and the fruits and the canneries.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where'd you first play ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: You had a sandlot ball around here?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had a little team.
[SPEAKER_01]: They called the Alpa Heights.
[SPEAKER_01]: We used to play the St. Louis...
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, a form of the St. Helena.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Dutch Juni was one of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was also a ballplayer professional.
[SPEAKER_01]: Juni, J-U-N-I-Y.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's dead now.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's been gone quite a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had us around 19... 6 and 7 and 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: What position did you play in those days?
[SPEAKER_01]: First base, always first base.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you have a high school here at Napa you went to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play on the team there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I got caught without a mask one day and that finished me in third catchment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, what happened?
[SPEAKER_01]: I got hit in the eye.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why didn't you have a mask on?
[SPEAKER_01]: We didn't have any masks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_01]: We didn't have any.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or at least if they forgot it, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you went on to St. Mary's, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: St. Mary's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did you plan to do at St. Mary's?
[SPEAKER_01]: What was your major field?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you have anything in particular?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was in the banking at St. Mary's.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a course there, a banking course.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except that, and then I went into baseball.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a pretty good team there, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_01]: They might, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they had a pretty good team.
[SPEAKER_01]: We used to play the Coast League during spring training.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you ever beat them?
[SPEAKER_01]: Once in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think we ever did while I was playing, but the team before me did, and they had some pretty good players, like Tiny Leonard and Dutch Leonard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dutch Leonard, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, they beat the Red Sox at 2-1.
[SPEAKER_01]: They keep giving two to one.
[SPEAKER_01]: They come out and they were training out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play ball all year round out here in the good weather or most of the year?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, most of the year we played.
[SPEAKER_01]: I noticed in the recent draft judges, so many of them come from the west coast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: The weather is so, you know, you can play most of the year, every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: What year did you finish up at St. Mary's then?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that was... 1915 or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sixteen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sixteen?
[SPEAKER_01]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sixteen.
[SPEAKER_01]: And who signed you for Cleveland?
[SPEAKER_01]: Two of the students at St. Mary's.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not for Cleveland, but for Portland.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why I started with Portland.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cleveland, Mr. Bernard, he was the vice president of Cleveland.
[SPEAKER_01]: He signed me for him.
[SPEAKER_01]: To see you?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, to see the managers of the Portland club.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't know anything about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this McCready running Portland?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Walter McCready.
[SPEAKER_01]: His uncle, I think, was the president.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the St. Mary's students recommended you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Two of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Both of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're both alive, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Portland signed you then?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was your first year in football?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the first year.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1916?
[SPEAKER_02]: 1916, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it a pretty big thrill going up there to the Coast League?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I can't remember very much of it now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, of course it was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were at the spring training, Sacramento III of Charlie Holliker.
[SPEAKER_01]: Carson Bigby and myself for three years.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't have very many, what they called, butchers in those days, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a few of us.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one of the three of us went up in the big leagues.
[SPEAKER_01]: Holliday was the good one, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: He was suffering a lot with him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he just thought he was sick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he was a beautiful player.
[SPEAKER_02]: There used to be pictures of him in the sporting news when he was just coming up, about the great future, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Bernard signed you then, is that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get much money from Cleveland?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not very much, not very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you join the team then, the end of the season?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not the end of the season, during the season, in August I think it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Met him in Chicago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was their first baseman?
[SPEAKER_01]: Gando.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he just died recently.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was in Calistoga.
[SPEAKER_01]: His home was Berkeley, I think, originally from Berkeley.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you got a few games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, a few, not very many.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then the war came on and
[SPEAKER_01]: That finished it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, did you go to training in 17?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Down in New Orleans?
[SPEAKER_02]: I trained in New Orleans.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got in, it says here, about 73 games that year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty good, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but you got to be playing every day.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game, you got to be playing every day.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't be from one day to the other, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lee Fole was managing the team tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Lee Fole.
[SPEAKER_01]: How'd you like him?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I liked him very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: And after, Speaker was kind of a...
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess I hear, who was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: George Uley or somebody told me that the speaker used to really call the shots almost from center field occasionally for a fall on the bench.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like pitcher changes, so I'd go along with the speaker.
[SPEAKER_02]: All you had was Jack Rainey was his name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jack Rainey was there, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Steve O'Neill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Womby was there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joe Womby.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a faculty neighbor of ours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joe Sewell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Chapman was there first.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joe Seward.
[SPEAKER_01]: Barry Gardner.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was thinking about it last night.
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw a little of the tape from the television.
[SPEAKER_01]: When he hits a ball, he'd look at it before he threw it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what he was doing, but he'd always get it there ahead of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Kowalewski?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Stanley.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's still going strong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we interviewed him out in South Bend.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where do you live in Manuka?
[SPEAKER_01]: South Bend.
[SPEAKER_01]: South Bend, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Indiana, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Used to live in Pecorino.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shemokin.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shemokin, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: He goes fishing.
[SPEAKER_02]: O'Neal's from Manuka.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kovaleski goes fishing every day in good weather.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We saw Joey Sewell last year down in Tuscaloosa.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the week before I went up to the Hall of Fame.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened to Luke?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's in good shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's in Akron, Ohio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I spent a morning with him a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's a...
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a very nice guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, a very nice boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a little boss Stevenson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we talked to him in Tuscaloosa.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you go to Tuscaloosa?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neighbor Joey Seals.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: He played football.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play football sometimes?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Riggins, Stevenson, and Joey Shore, that was convenient there, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alabama had some great ball teams there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get Joe Evans?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's a doctor in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was in infield 11?
[SPEAKER_01]: Outfield 11.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elmer Smith.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was pretty close to Joe Evans, was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they mentioned him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, no, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I met Elmer back in France during the war.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was with the mortuary outfit.
[SPEAKER_01]: His friends.
[SPEAKER_01]: I met Elmer over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much time did you put in?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: 14 months, I think, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: 15 months.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just slows you up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd like to get a picture of what we were talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's proof.
[SPEAKER_02]: So did that affect your career?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it slowed me up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get wounded over there?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was gassed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I got gassed in Belgium.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, yes, it slowed me up quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, nearly all the ballplayers were from active action, you know, sort of, but bound to, to carry that rifle along and weigh about nine pounds, you know, and all the steps to go through.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't play ball during that time either, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: When did you come back in 19?
[SPEAKER_02]: 19, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you play ball at all for a while there?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I went back to
[SPEAKER_01]: The next year I went back to Cleveland, but I was a sailor.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still belonged.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the year they won the pennants, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: 1920.
[SPEAKER_02]: You still have property there?
[SPEAKER_01]: I still have property, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play with some of the miners there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oakland.
[SPEAKER_01]: They loaned me to Oakland.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I went back up there.
[SPEAKER_01]: In 23, I came back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The parts of 22 and 23 are up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play much ball after that on the Coastal?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played with Oakland, finished with Oakland, up until 1927.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you played then on Averill and those guys with the Seals?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Seals, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was quite a far house.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'll tell you, they had a good ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gilbreath and... Roy Johnson.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had a good ball club.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a good league.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Coastal was a good league.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who was your manager at Oakland?
[SPEAKER_01]: Ivan Howard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he was at the St. Louis Browns in Cleveland.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a infielder, second baseman.
[SPEAKER_01]: His brother Dale was with the Cubs for years.
[SPEAKER_01]: He didn't know that he was not, but Ivan Howard, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah, he was with the Browns for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: How would you play?
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard in the coach that when you were saved with playing the Seals,
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't have the same ballpark they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oakland had their own.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Oakland had their own ballpark.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they used to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: On Thursday, the women that was visiting would play in Oakland Thursday afternoon and Sunday morning in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Sunday morning in Oakland.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thursday and Sunday morning they played in Oakland and we'd go to San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sunday morning?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sunday morning, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a big deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was very good.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of people came out to see it on Sunday morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: You had a long series, though, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Over 200 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: We played way over 200 games, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did Tony Lozari have his big year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, with Salt Lake.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how about Paul Strand?
[SPEAKER_01]: Paul Strand.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was breaking my hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened then?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the ball was thrown up the line, see?
[SPEAKER_01]: And Paul was coming down, and I reached in to get the ball and hit him.
[SPEAKER_01]: up my wrist in three or four places.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a long time I couldn't use that hand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, sure did.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's funny, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: The number of players that fit that category.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I think a lot of it is mental, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: They get up there with the biggies and start thinking about it, instead of going right along like they used to.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, you have to.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had everything for him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was he a solid too?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there something about the atmosphere up there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was light.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had to get over the fence with his fists.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked the playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's high.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had a Leveri at 60 on runs, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He never was a home run hitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Earl Sheeley and Bunny Grief.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bunny Grief.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember him?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Glenn Wright.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had some stories about finding grief.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look at him.
[SPEAKER_01]: He came from Traverse City, Michigan.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he's a, I think he's Griefalowski.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was that right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Griefalowski.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of those Polish felons cut their names down, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wonder where he got that burning from.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very masquerading.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he's a good-looking guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, who were some of the stars that coached the others?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's see... Mayos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Dustin Mayos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He dropped clear in 1920.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: He won the Panathon.
[SPEAKER_01]: He just passed away a year or two ago, a couple of years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know Jimmy O'Donnell?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: O'Connell.
[SPEAKER_02]: O'Connell, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a tragic thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever talked with him about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: We passed through Bakersfield and I was thinking I'd stop and talk to him, but I'd be mad and he wouldn't let me.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that was a terrible thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was just a, you know, innocent kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He shouldn't have done it, but he didn't really know what he was doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, of course not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Landis was kind of... Landis was a rough one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I suppose that kind of thing happening so soon after the Blackstocks made Landis... Sure did.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably overreacted, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_01]: Talk about czar, he was one, believe me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never had another one.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not like him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you bat against Walter Jensen?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that an experience?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I'm not mistaken, I think I did pretty well against him.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, Rick Owens was on par, and I was hitting him pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Line drive, but at somebody, and I said,
[SPEAKER_01]: I said, what's the matter?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're hitting everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Grab somebody.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said, well, you're hitting the ball too good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's too good.
[SPEAKER_01]: The ball come over too good, see?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't know anything about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jack Graney was an unknown cricket counselor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He would choke up, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Place it around the field?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Jack usually gets either two base hit or a three base hit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then there was Charlie Jamison.
[SPEAKER_02]: He took Graney's place.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's their dad that used to say about Jameson.
[SPEAKER_02]: We grew up in Cleveland, so that's why.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm particularly interested in talking to you because I didn't see you play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't call you any of that, but I knew something about their history, and their father used to see them in their twenties in Jameson.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said they'd bump the ball down the first base line and keep it right between his legs.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'd get away for a bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a great ballpark, that 66th and 11th.
[SPEAKER_01]: A good ballpark.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if the pitchers liked that right field wall too well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it was a great hitting ballpark.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was no signage or anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everything was green.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_01]: No seats in center field.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was less center, but you wouldn't lose the ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they had a good background.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I enjoyed New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's right at the heart of a ghetto right now, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I guess it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember we used to go through Wade Park in those days.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess you don't dare do that now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's old.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that where you stayed when you... No, no, I stayed on 55th and Lexington.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a hotel there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you remember the old Pennsylvania?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a drive-thru right by it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's changed, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I bet it has.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you know George Uly?
[SPEAKER_01]: Very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: He lives in Wambi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he lives in a bay village just outside Clayton.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I think Wambi lives in Lakewood.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Lakewood.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I was born and raised.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually interviewed Wambi back in the 1930s when I was writing my junior high school newspaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know what I was doing then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's a very fine man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uly had a lot of
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a good hitter, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I think he was more proud of his hitting than his pitching.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he was a very good hitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: He used to pitch hit quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that was nice, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jim Bagby, Tom Olenski, and Ed Kletfer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You went with him, of course, in the World Series, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: a wild play that happened then.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_02]: When Chapman got killed.
[SPEAKER_02]: He only saw that Ray Caldwell got struck by lightning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Top of his cap, and you could see the sparks come out of his spikes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they tell that story.
[SPEAKER_01]: I told them several times.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, people look at you.
[SPEAKER_01]: They must be nuts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was right, because there's a rubber, see, out there, see?
[SPEAKER_01]: Standing on the rubber.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a little metal.
[SPEAKER_01]: You used to have a little metal button on the top of your cap.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying to think of even... Oh, Fritz Krumbe was a left-hander.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think of another job here.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fritz, I don't think he had a job here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got a directory in the cave.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's where they live.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying to think of... Yeah, another left-hander.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jared Smith.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had a move that wouldn't be allowed today, first base.
[SPEAKER_01]: A move at first base.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd better get off there before he got you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It wasn't allowed today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you work on kickoff plays for the Pitchers?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I didn't have to.
[SPEAKER_01]: The difference I find today is there's more stars
[SPEAKER_01]: on one club.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whereas in the old days, it'd be one, maybe one or two, so you'd stir out.
[SPEAKER_01]: But in this day, you'd find four or five on one ball club.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then, of course, the ball being more lively, I think, had a lot to do with it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Swing for the fences, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jameson.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have about, oh, 15 or 18 nephews right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's a beautiful town here.
[SPEAKER_01]: This used to be nothing but an apple orchard.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: When I was younger, the population was about 2,000, but we never locked any doors or anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Never.
[SPEAKER_01]: Times have changed.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a nice town.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a nice talent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did you, any other pitchers you remember batting against?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Herbert Shocker, Brett Faber.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Will Spitballer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I can hit Spitballer, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I broke in against Spitballer, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Phil Steen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he was at Cleveland years ago, and he was out, he'd finish stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Steen, Steven, Krap, Parkness, and that was a great pitcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Portland's pitching staff, very, very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dean Gregg, he was a great pitcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was he on the way down then or the way up?
[SPEAKER_01]: He was on his way up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then he went to Cleveland.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then there was Gus Fisher.
[SPEAKER_01]: He went to Cleveland, catcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think he was at Cleveland, over at Hayworth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know Roger Peckinpah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I met him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know him very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: He came over later on, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he was part of them, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, he was very early.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there was Olsen, Bancroft, Peckinpah.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had short east time, we had short south at Cleveland.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did you like the umpires?
[SPEAKER_02]: Any of them stand out in your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I liked them all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gilbert Rand was from out here, you know, in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_01]: Conley, Evans, Rick Owens, Bill Guthrie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh boy, he was a dandy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll never forget in Salt Lake, he was umpiring out here.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I disputed his decision.
[SPEAKER_01]: I put my hand on my head and said, listen, Dewey, remember this.
[SPEAKER_01]: The clothes of the umpire are as sacred as the robes of the Pope.
[SPEAKER_01]: I never forgot it.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a good umpire, Dewey.
[SPEAKER_01]: An excellent umpire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, did he put you out of the game anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he never put me out of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Q.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's quite an achievement.
[SPEAKER_02]: A. Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I tell you, I had a lot of respect for umpires.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a tough job.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't please them all, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this one particular one, it stuck out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll never forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Q.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did Sokolovsky come out here?
[SPEAKER_01]: A. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, he was back there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Byron came out here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bill Barnes.
[SPEAKER_01]: He used to throw that indicator up all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can't hit the ball with the bat on his shoulder.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a good umpire, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sheridan?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, he was O'Day and Sheridan, I think, were through then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sheridan, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he's passed away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Coast League, you have some of these player umpires started out here that went up then, I guess, like Guthrie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Guthrie and Hill LeBrand, Pennelly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dave Pennelly, he lives up in Sonoma.
[SPEAKER_01]: Boy Springs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that very far from here?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's 12 miles.
[SPEAKER_01]: 12 miles.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he was up there.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a good umpire.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was up there a good ball player, yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was his real name, was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Polinelli.
[SPEAKER_02]: Took out a couple of syllables.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rinaldo Polinelli.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the newspaper didn't do that, you know, they cut it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's too long for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't there an old player named Asbjørnsson who became Asby?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who?
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody named Asbjørnsson, a Norwegian singer, who played for him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody told me that story.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's up briefly, Asbjørnsson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, did you have any humorous incidents you recall in the baseball field, either?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not very many.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were in the Coast League.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's something funny that seems to be happening all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Amazing plays.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I saw one player, Mickey Cochran, maybe, in Portland.
[SPEAKER_01]: scoring and the catcher was down to catch and receive the ball, he jumped over onto the plate.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's quite a feat.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that's, I don't see very many of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, one, one that came up to Salt Lake, they were going, you know, very badly, and he was scoring runs.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what they did was pile up bats up in a teepee form, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a newspaper, but it only started at five.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any big thrills that stand out in your mind based on any big games or great plays?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I mean, it was kind of routine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I broke in my first ball pitch, and I luckily hit it over the fence, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You caught it in the net?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, when I broke in.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's about the way I broke in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's the way to break in.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I was kind of frail there.
[SPEAKER_01]: What, uh, that wasn't Multnomah Park, was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that was over in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, that was one of the... See, we played over in... Oakland played in San Francisco except Thursday and Sunday morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, San Francisco was the big one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'd play Sunday morning, and we'd take the ferry and go over and play in the afternoon, ferrying off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Down in L.A., there were... Vernon had a team down there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Vernon, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Hollywood didn't have... No, there was no Hollywood then.
[SPEAKER_02]: In L.A.?
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a ballpark in Los Angeles, right there in town.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't remember the street, Hill Street, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Would that be the Wrigley Park, or was that another... No, no, that's... Wrigley, oh, that's that street.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this, when I played there,
[SPEAKER_01]: The ballpark was right in the center of town.
[SPEAKER_01]: That land would be, you couldn't buy it now, of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then over the left-field fence, the studios of television had, not television, but movie studios had a wild animal thing that they used in their pictures.
[SPEAKER_01]: And over the left-field fence.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you do in the off-season?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hunting?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fishing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I did a lot of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fishing, a lot of bail-up and climbing.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got things done.
[SPEAKER_01]: There really wasn't anything to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a small town and everybody had a job.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wouldn't give you a job because you're going to be playing ball next year, is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's to buy me a few drugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: There wasn't anywhere that wasn't permanent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were there...
[SPEAKER_02]: training while at school, you might have had some opportunities there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know Carl Mays?
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't get to know him, did you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I used to know him.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I didn't know him.
[SPEAKER_01]: We used to spend some time, though, Carl Mays.
[SPEAKER_01]: At that time, when I knew him, he was at Boston Red Sox.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Groot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a great picture of him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Groot and Mays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ernie Shore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keith Gedeon and Joe Wood.
[SPEAKER_01]: He lost his pitching line.
[SPEAKER_02]: He lost his pitching line.
[SPEAKER_02]: He talked to Ernie Schorr down in North Carolina because he had a perfect game, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they had a good pitching staff, the Red Sox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy, he showed them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about after baseball, what did you do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I went, uh, I coached at St. Mary's, coached baseball there for a number of years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I operated the student store, bookstore, and, you know, odds and ends.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I kept me pretty busy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I retired in about 1960.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, uh, where you live, uh, how far away is St. Mary's?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's, uh, what's about 40 to 45 miles.
[SPEAKER_01]: in Milwaukee.
[SPEAKER_01]: From San Francisco it would be about 21 miles.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a beautiful place.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all built up.
[SPEAKER_01]: When we were out there, the pioneers went out there, the colonels went out there and moved from Oakland in 1929.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was nothing else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Petaluma?
[SPEAKER_00]: Petaluma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Petaluma, California.
[SPEAKER_02]: Petaluma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Petaluma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Petaluma.
[SPEAKER_02]: I put an N in it, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a little bit north of San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: K08 campground here on Route 101 or something like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: On Saturday night, June 24th.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had this interview with Louis Guisto earlier today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was not scheduled, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: We spent last night at Lodi, which is about 110 miles away, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we drove on over this morning on a lovely day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we thought we'd try Napa, where Guisto lives.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if not Napa, then up to Boys Springs, where Penelli lives, or Glen Ellen, where Mark Koenig lives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then we thought we'd maybe come over here after that or else come over here before that and go back and make the interviews later.
[SPEAKER_02]: We weren't quite sure what the plan would be.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we got into Napa and got out to Guisto's house about quarter of 11.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The garage was empty.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the spray was going in the front lawn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went up and knocked on the door.
[SPEAKER_02]: No answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: A gentleman from across the street came over and said that he saw that we were from West Virginia.
[SPEAKER_02]: make sure we knew what the story was.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he said Guisto had gone out shortly before and should be back very soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though he was in his 80s, he was in good shape physically and would be disappointed if we hadn't seen him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we thought about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then we went into town and got something to eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: We hadn't eaten much.
[SPEAKER_02]: We went into the butter, not dairy, butterflower bakery, I guess it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Had some coffee and donuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then came back out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was about 11.30 now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked to somebody else who said he should be back.
[SPEAKER_02]: We waited out in the car.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were going to leave after about 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he pulled in about then.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the gentleman next door came rushing out to tell him that there were some visitors from West Virginia, which didn't seem to thrill him greatly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he acknowledged us and invited us in.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he was kind of rushed.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a very ill sister.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he had other things to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he could give us a little bit of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we sat down there about 11.30 and had the half hour tape, the other side of this tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't much to it, but at least I talked to him and I heard him.
[SPEAKER_02]: He signed the ball, and we got a couple pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, could you describe the house?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a stone house with a little
[SPEAKER_00]: porch-like affair coming out in front, a veranda-type thing that was covered with ivy that was thicker than your arm, the stalks.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said you could take off the porch pillars, and the ivy stalks would hold up the roof.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: And inside the house, it was very nicely furnished, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not modern, by any means, but traditional furniture.
[SPEAKER_00]: and pictures all over of nieces and nephews.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think he has 15 nephews living in Napa alone.
[SPEAKER_00]: In the dining room, it was a traditional dining room thing with a lace tablecloth on it, a plastic tablecloth on top of that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the sideboard, or the buffet, was loaded with liquor bottles.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so were all the ashtrays loaded with, they had all been used.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then that little kitchen or den, whatever it was,
[SPEAKER_00]: was piled high with papers and books.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looked like your type of journal, whatever was in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe desk bookkeeping on the side or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit of clutter out there in the back rooms.
[SPEAKER_00]: But not in the living room.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was except for the pictures, which were all over Kingdom Come.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, they must be Catholic, because they have a Madonna and child up there and a crucifix.
[SPEAKER_00]: And has no children of his own.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whether he was married or not, we never did find out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we know one younger sister and one older sister.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the younger sister has six grandchildren or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's when he said he had 15 to 18 nephews in the valley in Napa.
[SPEAKER_02]: The front of the house is covered with bushes and trees and shrubbery.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can hardly see the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I walked around the back where this other gentleman spoke to me, and he had looked rather cluttered in the back with bushes and trees.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't see any lawn or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe he's got an orchard and some vines of his own out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's a very good health for his age.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't look 83.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a little hunched over, very stouty, always a stout.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gray hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rather firm features and a firm manner.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember his pictures back in the 20s with a mustache.
[SPEAKER_02]: He seemed so unusual wearing a mustache then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't have one now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he still was recognizable, though, as I recall those old pictures.
[SPEAKER_00]: But he didn't even tell any good stories after we left.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, after the tape went off.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I think he was surprised that you left as soon as it switched off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just got that impression that he was surprised you were ready to leave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I felt that he wanted me to leave.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was kind of an imposition coming in like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I said, do you have some time?
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, well, a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I said, well, he said, how much time?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, maybe an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he looked at his watch and said, well, just an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: So from that clue, I felt imposed to take a half an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't think he was unhappy to quit then.
[SPEAKER_02]: The living room was dark.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were no lights on in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought we might take some – we did take a couple pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope they came out, but there wasn't much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of gloomy in a way.
[SPEAKER_00]: But he didn't have any pictures of himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just had one of those cut-out post-board ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: When he played it open?
[SPEAKER_02]: was standing up, which was over in the mantelpiece.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was all he had.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, he wasn't up that long, was he?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he played quite a few years in the Coast League, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, his career ran over 10 or 12 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he was lost some time in the war.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I had heard that he'd been gassed in the war, and this really affected his career.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he had a couple of injuries, too, at the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody ran into him there and broke his hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he had some misfortunes, which certainly affected his career.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't, I don't know, he didn't seem to have too much of a sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know that I expected this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty cut and dry, the whole business.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I didn't really have any desire to drag it out much longer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Covered the ground as best we could in half an hour, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably the longest interview he's ever had, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about the shortest one I've had.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think we've covered the ground on him.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got about 20 minutes to go on this side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, after we left him, it was around 12, 15 or so, we drove into Sonoma, which was Thornton Lee's hometown, whom we interviewed a couple of days ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, a couple of weeks ago, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before Palm Springs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We found Sonoma a very attractive town, quite historic.
[SPEAKER_02]: A plaza that looked like a real Spanish, laid-out town, much like Santa Fe had been.
[SPEAKER_02]: These low, historic buildings circumventing the square.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some historic buildings.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the monument where the Bear Flag Republic was raised back in 1846, the Announcement of the Independence of California, which was promptly repudiated by the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: For a brief month or so, there was a
[SPEAKER_02]: in the independent state of California.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on the square.
[SPEAKER_02]: The home of Yeho.
[SPEAKER_00]: I never knew who he was.
[SPEAKER_00]: He was the one who was governor, or whatever it was, when they raised the bear flag.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the missionary is the northernmost missionary on the Mission Trail.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would have been nice to see that missionary.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what happened was we got a little concerned about a place to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other interviews, I tried to call Babe Penelope and got all kinds of a run around, and I never could find her.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was long.
[SPEAKER_02]: About 2 o'clock, we decided to find a place to stay and then maybe see Sonora better or completely.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a winery we wanted to go through.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the one motel in town was taken.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we drove over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the time we got here, we got all set up.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just didn't feel like going back there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everything would have been closed, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we might have barely made it, but it probably would have been time for a tour of the winery.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know what else we could have seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we probably should have done something else, but that's the way it worked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't get the Penelli interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Mark Koenig has got his name in the phone book, but I don't know that we'll be able to see him.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to get going home one of these days, and I think we're going to start tomorrow as we go farther north and west.
[SPEAKER_02]: We keep getting farther away from home as we go home.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we got to go farther away to start back.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the only way we can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you want to cross the great, what do they call it, the great alkali desert or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess that's about it on the Louis Guisto interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't the greatest interview, but I
[SPEAKER_02]: did satisfy a desire I'd long had to meet Billy Guisto.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tomorrow it's on the road up north, and maybe we'll have a great interview with Joe Oscar, who's probably 88.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Ferndale.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he pitched in that long game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see, but that's all for this time.